

Bhagya Shree Chouhan

React Developer

A positive and motivated individual committed to excellence and successful outcomes. Hi, I have been learning and developing React-based applications for less than one year (want to become a Full-Stack developer one day). I am interested in coding, developing and designing.

Work Experience

Jr. React Developer



July 2021 - Present at Moverstrip Digital Service

- Design and Develop HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, and React JS that meets web browser standards for website.
- Knowledge about and learning experience of using props, states and other ES6 features.
- Design and Develop My Portfolio in React JS.
- Basic Knowledge about React Redux and other features.
- Basic knowledge about api methods, hooks, functional components in React.
- Learn how to maintained states using Redux.
- Worked as Graphic Designer, help in designing visual layout of mobile app and website, social media post design, logo etc.

Junior IT Engineer

Sept. 2019-Jan. 2021 - at Toshniwal Industries Pvt Ltd.

- Worked as IT support engineer.
- · Work on Java

Contact

Contact:

8949344560

Email:

bhagyashreechouhan248@gmail.com

Address:

Behind new All Saint School, Dholabata Road, Ajmer, Rajasthan (305001)

Skills

- React
- Redux
- Web Development
- App Development
- Photoshop
- Graphic Designer

- HTML, CSS
- JavaScript(ES6)
- Node.js
- Front-End Coding
- Digital Marketing

Education History

B. Tech (Information Technology)

(RTU, Kota) Aggregate - 71% 2015-2019

Sr. Secondary

(RBSE)

Percentage - 84% 2013-2014

Secondary

(RBSE)

Percentage - 84% 2012-2013

github.com/shreebhagya24

bhagya-shree-chouhan358525187